http://www.monistat.com/privacy-policy#section-4

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement
Last updated January 2, 2020.
Prestige Consumer Healthcare Inc. (including each of its subsidiaries, collectively, "Prestige Consumer Healthcare" or "we" or "our") is committed to respecting your data privacy. Our Privacy Policy (also referred to as “Policy” or “Policy Statement”) is designed to inform you about the manner in which we collect and process personal data and other information in connection with your use of the Prestige Consumer Healthcare website (www.prestigebrands.com) as well as to other websites in the Prestige Consumer Healthcare family of websites (collectively, "Site" or "Sites"). By visiting our Site, you are accepting the term of our Privacy Policy. Please note that our Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party sites which may be linked to from our Site.
Content Overview:
What information is captured from visitors to prestigebrands.com and its brands' Sites?
What personally identifiable information is collected from me?
How is my information used?
Does Prestige Consumer Healthcare use cookies, Interested-Based Advertising, Do Not Track and similar tracking technologies?
Who is collecting my information?
With whom does Prestige Consumer Healthcare share my information?
How do I access, update or delete my information?
What does "opt-out" mean?
What happens when I leave prestigebrands.com to visit a linked website?
What happens if I e-mail Prestige Consumer Healthcare?
Is my information secure?
How do I contact Prestige Consumer Healthcare?
What else should I know about my privacy?
Notice regarding changes to Privacy Statement.
Other legal notices.
1. What information is captured from visitors to the Site?
For each visitor to the Site, Prestige Consumer Healthcare may collect information that indirectly may identify you. Such information may include which pages within our Site are visited and for how long, your internet protocol (IP) address, mobile device ID, browser type, and operating platform. This information may be used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and to improve your user experience of our Site. We also may provide this information (as well as information from third-party market researchers) about our users on an aggregated, anonymous basis to our affiliates and strategic partners.
2. What personally identifiable information is collected from me?
We only solicit personal information from Site visitors on a voluntary basis. On certain pages of our Sites, you can make requests and/or receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your name, e-mail address and standard contact information, including addresses and phone numbers. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with the products and services we provide, product preferences, and contact preferences. Prestige Consumer Healthcare does not require this information to obtain access to any part of our Site. Certain of our Sites may allow you to link to a third-party website to make purchases. If you choose to link to a third-party website to make purchases, those websites may collect your personal information (such as payment information as well as other contact information).
Prestige Consumer Healthcare has no intention of collecting any personal data from individuals under 13 years of age. Recognizing that under some circumstances children may be able to access this Site, Prestige Consumer Healthcare will not collect personal information that is not anonymized from any child under the age of 13 without parental/guardian consent, and if collected, upon the request of parent/guardian, Prestige Consumer Healthcare will make reasonable efforts to delete such information.
3. How is my information used?
Personal information collected from you through the Site is used by Prestige Consumer Healthcare to enable us to answer questions and process requests that are received electronically. We also may use this information to send you e-mail or other notices about updates to the Site or our products or services. You will always have the option to opt-out of any such mailing list. Prestige Consumer Healthcare will not sell, rent, lease or otherwise make available your personally identifiable information to others without your consent, except as provided for or referenced in this Policy. In general, the information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with Prestige Consumer Healthcare. Your information may be shared with agents, contractors or business partners for the purpose of performing services for Prestige Consumer Healthcare.
We want to help you quickly find information on Prestige Consumer Healthcare and alert you to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and services from Prestige Consumer Healthcare. Accordingly, we may send you direct mailings about our various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply "opt-out" by the means provided for in the mailings. If you have communicated with us through this Site and wish to have personal information removed, please write us at:
Prestige Consumer Healthcare Inc.
Office of Consumer Affairs
660 White Plains Road, Suite #250
Tarrytown, NY 10591
Or visit our Contact Us page and send an e-mail.
4. Does Prestige Consumer Healthcare use cookies, Interest-Based Advertising, Do Not Track and similar tracking technologies?
Cookies and Similar Technologies
Prestige Consumer Healthcare may allow third-party service providers to use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other technologies to collect your information and to track browsing activity over time and across third party websites, including for the purpose of providing you with Interest-Based Advertising (see below for more information). The providers of these services may use your IP address or an anonymous identifier as well as certain information from your browser, together with other non-personal information about your visits to our Site and other websites, in order to provide analytical information for our Site and other websites.
You may opt-out of tracking technologies on this website by clicking here, then clicking on “Settings” and deselecting some or all of the services listed. For additional support or to request that any information collected from you be deleted, please email privacy@prestigebrands.com.
DO NOT SELL MY INFORMATION
Like many other Companies, we currently use Google Analytics to collect information about our Sites. Traffic and usage data collected by Google (obtained through the use of Google cookies on the Sites) is subject to Google's privacy policy. Per the applicable Google Analytics service terms, Google does not collect personally identifiable information in connection with those services. Note that Google offers a Google Analytics browser add-on (designed to be compatible only with certain browsers) to provide Site visitors the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. That add-on may be obtained here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en; and other privacy controls are available here: www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html.
Interest-Based Advertising
We may work with third party advertising companies that gather information about your visits to the Site and elsewhere on the Internet. These ad companies may use this information to provide you with more relevant advertising, content, and for other advertising related purposes. For more information about third party advertising networks, visit http://www.aboutads.info/consumers. To opt-out of certain targeted advertising, visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. Once you click the link, you may choose to opt-out of such advertising from all participating advertising companies or only advertising provided by specific advertising companies. If you opt-out of this type of advertising, you will still see advertising on the Internet and advertising from Prestige Consumer Healthcare, but those ads may not be tailored to your Site usage and may be less relevant to you.
Other than as described herein, Prestige Consumer Healthcare does not track your activity over time and across different websites or online services except as among the related websites that constitute the Prestige Consumer Healthcare Site and as otherwise described herein.
Do Not Track
The Do Not Track ("DNT") privacy preference, which is offered by some web browsers (http://donottrack.us/), allows you to opt-out of tracking by websites and online services. Prestige Consumer Healthcare does not currently recognize DNT signals. Therefore, the Prestige Consumer Healthcare information collection and disclosure practices and your choices regarding our collection and disclosures will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Statement, whether or not a DNT signal is received.
We do not permit our third-party service providers to collect information from the Site for other websites or for their own purposes other than as described herein.
5. Who is collecting my information?
When you are on a Prestige Consumer Healthcare Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Prestige Consumer Healthcare and our authorized partners strictly for Prestige Consumer Healthcare use, unless specifically stated otherwise.
6. With whom does Prestige Consumer Healthcare share my information?
We may share the personal data you provide with other Prestige Consumer Healthcare agents, contractors or our business partners for the purposes of performing services for Prestige Consumer Healthcare. Prestige Consumer Healthcare also may share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. We also believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, pursuant to our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. Except as provided in this Privacy Statement or in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale or transfer of all or a material portion of Prestige Consumer Healthcare' assets, we will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission.
7. How do I access, update or delete my information?
You may opt out of tracking or data collection by clicking here to access your privacy controls. For further support, please email us at privacy@prestigebrands.com.
8. What does "opt-out" mean?
To "opt-out" means that you have notified Prestige Consumer Healthcare that we no longer have permission to use your information for a particular purpose. For example, when we send you information on a new product, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving such information in the future.
9. What happens when I leave prestigebrands.com to visit a linked website?
Parts of the Site include hyperlinks to the websites of other companies. When you leave prestigebrands.com to visit one of these websites, the only information transferred to the third party is the fact that you came from prestigebrands.com. This practice allows the third party to monitor its own website traffic, but does not provide it with any information about you. Prestige Consumer Healthcare is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of third party websites. You should consult the privacy policies at third party websites to determine how your information may be used.
10. What happens if I e-mail Prestige Consumer Healthcare?
Prestige Consumer Healthcare may provide e-mail links on its Sites to further facilitate communication between Prestige Consumer Healthcare and you. Information collected through electronic mail may be shared with our customer service department, employees or other third parties that perform services on our behalf. Unless otherwise noted, electronic mail on our Site is not a completely secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted electronic communications may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your knowledge or permission while in transit to us. Therefore, we recommend that you contact us by phone using one of the numbers found on our Sites whenever you are communicating personal information to us.
11. Is my information secure?
Prestige Consumer Healthcare has taken commercially reasonable measures to keep all information from our online visitors as secure as possible against any unauthorized access or use. All information is protected by standard security measures which are periodically reviewed. Unless otherwise noted, electronic mail on our Site is not a completely secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted electronic communications may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your knowledge or permission while in transit to us.
12. How do I contact Prestige Consumer Healthcare?
We can be reached via our Contact Us page.
13. What else should I know about my privacy?
Third-party web sites and services accessible through Prestige Consumer Healthcare have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Prestige Consumer Healthcare has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, Prestige Consumer Healthcare cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk.
Please be advised that Prestige Consumer Healthcare may transfer personal information it collects outside your country of domicile to jurisdictions where data protection and privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws of your country. BY USING OUR SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE TRANSFER AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.
Your California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83-1798.84 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by certain members of the Prestige Consumer Healthcare family of companies to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to privacy@prestigebrands.com or write us:
Prestige Consumer Healthcare Inc.
Office of Consumer Affairs
660 White Plains Road Suite #250
Tarrytown, NY 10591
14. Notice regarding changes to Privacy Statement.
Prestige Consumer Healthcare may, in its sole discretion, change this Privacy Statement from time to time. Any and all changes to the Prestige Consumer Healthcare Privacy Statement will be reflected here and the date new versions are posted will be stated at the top of this Privacy Statement. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on the Site. If you do not agree with this Privacy Statement, please do not use or access the Site, and if you do not agree to any changes we make in the future, you must end your use of the Site.
Where language on the Site contradicts that found in this Privacy Statement, this Privacy Statement shall prevail. This Privacy Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.
15. Other Legal Notices.
Any dispute over privacy is subject to the privacy policy then in effect at the time the dispute arises, as well as the laws of the State of New York and our Terms of Use. If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this Policy, please send us a thorough description to:
Prestige Consumer Healthcare Inc.
Office of Consumer Affairs
660 White Plains Road Suite #250
Tarrytown, NY 10591
